Ravneet Kaur

220 North Main Street, Adrian MI 49221 (872) 855-6441 | aforeverai@gmail.com

Date available to begin work: Immediately

SUMMARY STATEMENT

My experience starts with a TEDxOrangeCoast presentation and moves forward into serving as an appointed public official, set to run academic policy for the State of California. My team-oriented mindset, attention to detail and several years of administrative work experience are qualities that are welcomed in an a collaborative work environment.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Education Bachelor of Arts in Sociology from University of California, Berkeley.

Relevant Experience Built up to be a leader, versed in technology and sociology. i have tutored folks in C++/Java, have coded

in Python. I am taking a Java bootcamp, course covering Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScrpit, Databases, Eclispe, IdeaJ, SQL, Selenium, Jenkins, Git/GitHub, JDBC, AWS Cloud, JIRA. - the course fully completes in 10 (ten) weeks, on May 26th. I have prior experience working with Java (1 year), HTML (4 years), Git (6 Months),

[JIRA, JSON, Confluence (7 months)], Python (5 months).

Personal Chat with me about refinement. i want code an auto-lawsuit app.

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

Ferraro, June 2022 – June 2022 Randstad USA, Chicago, IL Salary: \$17.68 per hour

Job Type: 40+ hours per week, Full- Time

i worked as a machine operator assisting with cone production for Keebler brand cones.

Clinical Laboratory Assistant, January 2022 – March 2022

Randstad USA, Millbrae, CA

Salary: \$32 per hour

Job Type: 40 hours per week, Full-Time

The automated instruments used are for the purposes of extraction, rna replication, and rna analysis; the instruments include Chemagics 360, Hamiltons, Agilent Technologies, Braavos. All machines are serviced and troubleshooted both weekly and daily.

Game Tester, January 2022 – March 2022 **NetEase**, Millbrae, CA **Salary**: varied

i was hired to test video games.

Sales Associate, February 2014 – February 2014

Athleta, San Francisco, CA

Job Type: Seasonal

i learned about materials, cycles of production, the feel of antibacterial silver, and captured an image of how to lay out the sales floor.

Research Analyst, December 2021 – January 2022 **International Bank**, Paris, France

Constructed a 80 page report analyzing the effect of COVID-19 on the economies of countries.

Software Support and Accessioner, May 2021 - November 2021

Opentrons Labworks Inc., Irvine, CA

Salary: \$75,000 per year

Job Type: 40+ hours per week, Full-Time

i automated the transition from one external PHI software to another external PHI software (data collector) prior to resignation here. i worked with UX, product managers, i can translate user pain points into cost - and know how to conduct user interviews.

The following are tasks i routinely and critically preformed:

i collaborated with lab staff to triage and correct problems using documented processes.

i troubleshot novel situations in consultation with lab staff and technicians from higher support tiers.

i proactively identify potential problem points and optimization opportunities.

i developed and documented processes and procedures to ensure consistent handling of error recovery in the lab pipeline.

i uploaded updates and new training to a document control platform - Confluence.

i worked to get feedback and use cases from the lab about our internal LIMS.

i assisted technologists and technicians with the operation of standard laboratory instruments.

i performed routine laboratory assistant duties according to agency standards and protocols.

Autopsist, February 2021 - September 2021

Illume Pathology and Autopsy Services, Hayward, CA

Salary: varied **Job Type**: Part-Time

Full body, chest, brain, autopsies were performed alone and shipped off to a lab for tissue analysis.

Covid Site Volunteer, January 2021 – February 2021

City of Rancho Cordova, CA

Salary: \$200 per day

Job Type: 20+ hours per week, Seasonal

i assisted members of the Rancho Cordova Community sign up for COVID-19 tests.

Paralegal, March 2020 - April 2020

The Law Offices of James V Cholous/Cholous Law Group, San Francisco, California

Salary: \$23.00 per hour

Job Type: 40 hours per week, Full-Time

i in-took clients, filled out form interrogatories, special interrogatories, and obtained medical record and medical bills.

Sales Associate, November 2019 - March 2020

Guitar Center, Riverside, California

i focused on software, setting up private music production lesson for Pro Tools, excelled at selling DJ equipment & both learned and validated knowledge about about microphones and speakers. i was second in amount credit card sign ups during my second month.

Research Analyst, March 2019 - June 2019

CRC Inc, New York, New York **Salary:** \$26.00 per hour

Job Type: 60 - 70 hours per week, Full-Time

i managed accounts on VRBO and Air BNB, served as a PA, helped set up a LLC, helped purchase properties as part of a division for micro-scale investor.

i helped the firm expand into investment by recommending and buying 3 properties with a 3 million dollar budget. i created and updated spreadsheets to keep track of properties eligible for purchase and outlined bimonthly projected

net income based on spaces occupied.

i assisted acquiring financing while outlining management plans for retail and residential properties purchased in Ohio and Brooklyn, New York.

i dealt with property mangers, appraisers, and financiers alongside a paralegal.

i managed emails and messages; acting as first point of contact with requests related to the necessary property documents needed for financing; while acting as the property manager of an Air BnB residential housing building.

i managed the CEO's inbox and phone calls

i developed a promotional campaign for attracting clients for the purchased retails buildings.

i initiated LLC's on behalf of the firm

i set up meetings and booked hotels, flights, rentals, and cars.

Member, February 2014 – Present

Board of Governors, Sacramento, California

Salary: \$100 per bi-monthly board meeting, did not expense a plethora of items.

Job Type: Full-Time

Supervisor: Jerry Brown, (916) 445-8752

Served as non-voting and subsequently as a voting member on the 17 and subsequently 16-member board which formally interacts with state and federal officials to set policy for California Community Colleges as a part of shared governance.

i attended 2-5 meetings a month in Sacramento in between adhocs, boards, and committees, which set the legislation for all 112 colleges that constituted the system, i am part of the cohort which recommended and released 4 year degrees at community colleges, i ate, collaborated, and worked closely with policy makers, mayors, trustees, senators, and elected officials, i attended multiple fundraisers, events, banquets, and galas. i attended 150+ meetings relating to shared governance and student life in college before i resigned to focus on University. Serving on the board when four (4) year degrees were trialed at two (2) year colleges, is the greatest experience i was part of by 2015.

Barista, June 2014 - June 2015

Starbucks Coffee Company Riverside, California

Salary: \$9.50 per hour

Job Type: 26 hours per week, Part-Time **Supervisor:** Heather Holding (951) 509-2673

Steaming liquids, quality control, timing sequences, are all the summation of my work at Starbucks Coffee Company; I earned substantial praise vis-á-vis management and customer feedback.

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Apprenticeship, Community Garden May 2022 - July 2022

i helped plant food for houseless populations in addition to scribing notes on growing techniques.

Assistant, Hyde Street Studios October 2020 - January 2021

i assisted in studio set up, in took calls from potential clients, and observed mixing and mastering.

Narrator, Vagina Monologues August 2017 - March 2018

Trained to engage with the audience consistently for the longest and largest production on campus.

Community Health Worker, May 2016 - June 2017

Berkeley, CA

i was present during the transition into an in house software consisting of a PHI database constructed by volunteer during my time

i shadowed the administration of Hepatitis A, Hepatitis B, Hepatitis C, TB, Flu Vaccines and HIV diagnoses; i preformed blood draws, i recall administering vaccines, i did not feel the position was a good fit after i was publicly pleasured to and indirectly asked to be a prostitute by two different bodies on the same evening.

i coordinated and facilitated medical sessions for members of the community, including homeless populations and needle users.

tested and administered results to vulnerable populations for HIV, HEP A, B, C and TB.

i generated and updated an interdepartmental spreadsheet daily that kept track of new clients, health reports which turned into electronic medical records.

i audited new clients to asses disease risks based on lifestyle and uploaded new clients information into storage database for record keeping.

i screened intake paper work and questionnaire forms as well as conducted interviews which led recommendations on which tests each client should take.

i fundraised 200 USD at the pride parade in San Francisco, California for the Berkeley Free Clinic.

i donated my MacBook Pro here.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Sociology, December 2018

University of California, Berkeley, CA, cGPA 3.2

CERTIFICATIONS/ACHIEVEMENTS

200+ hours of Community Service, Fall 2012, Spring 2012, Fall 2013, Spring 2013, Fall 2014, Spring 2014

Was recognized in a multi-district setting.

Binary Logic, May 2023

Java bootcamp, course covering Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScrpit, Databases, Eclispe, IdeaJ, SQL, Selenium, Jenkins, Git/GitHub, JDBC, AWS Cloud, JIRA, Ruby.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE / COMMUNITY SERVICE

Instructor at the University of California, Berkeley, Music 198, August 2018 - December 2018

Berkeley, CA

Designed and taught music production in the Albert Elkus Room in Morrison Hall. Students were required to compose an album.

Music Producer, The Daily Californian August 2018 – December 2018

Berkeley, CA

Developed content, videoed independent projects, and edited content.

Region IX Governance and Policy Senator July 2014 – July 2015

Sacramento, CA

Served as an elected student representative for the 112 colleges (now 116), which held 2.1 million students, in the law making and shared governance process for the state of California.

Prior to, and concurrent with this role, i was working with student senates on the local level as a Board of Commissioners Member, Board of Commissioners Director, Student Senator, and Senate Pro-Tempore.

TEDxOrangeCoast July 2014

Orange County, CA

Made an edible water bottle with a colleague which was presented at TEDxOrangeCoast.